convinceandconvert.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy | Convince and Convert: Social Media Consulting and Content Marketing Consulting

Convince & Convert, LLC (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the  
www.convinceandconvert.com website (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and  
disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have  
associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you  
agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.  
Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy  
Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from  
www.convinceandconvert.com

Definitions  
———–

Personal Data  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from  
those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or  
likely to come into our possession).

Usage Data  
~~~~~~~~~~

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the  
Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration  
of a page visit).

Cookies  
~~~~~~~

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

Data Controller  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with  
other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any  
personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

Data Processor (or Service Providers)  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee  
of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data  
Controller.

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your  
data more effectively.

Data Subject  
~~~~~~~~~~~~

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

User  
~~~~

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data  
Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

Information Collection And Use  
——————————

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to  
provide and improve our Service to you.

Types of Data Collected  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Personal Data  
*************

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally  
identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you  
(“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not  
limited to:

* Email address  
* First name and last name  
* Phone number  
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City (for contest giveaways only)  
* Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or  
promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you.  
You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by  
following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send  
or by contacting us.

Usage Data  
**********

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage  
Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s  
Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version,  
the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the  
time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic  
data.

Location Data  
*************

We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission  
to do so (“Location Data”). We use this data to provide features of our  
Service, to improve and customize our Service.

You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any  
time, through your device settings.

Tracking &amp; Cookies Data  
************

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our  
Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous  
unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored  
on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts  
to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a  
cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be  
able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.  
* Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences  
and various settings.  
* Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

Use of Data  
———–

Convince & Convert, LLC uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service  
* To notify you about changes to our Service  
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when  
you choose to do so  
* To provide customer support  
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our  
Service  
* To monitor the usage of our Service  
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues  
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about  
other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those  
that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted  
not to receive such information

Retention of Data  
—————–

Convince & Convert, LLC will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is  
necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and  
use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal  
obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply  
with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and  
policies.

Convince & Convert, LLC will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis  
purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time,  
except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the  
functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data  
for longer time periods.

Transfer Of Data  
—————-

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and  
maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or  
other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than  
those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to  
us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United  
States and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such  
information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Convince & Convert, LLC will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure  
that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy  
and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a  
country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of  
your data and other personal information.

Disclosure Of Data  
——————

Business Transaction  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

If Convince & Convert, LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale,  
your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your  
Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy  
Policy.

Disclosure for Law Enforcement  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Under certain circumstances, Convince & Convert, LLC may be required to  
disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to  
valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

Legal Requirements  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Convince & Convert, LLC may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith  
belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation  
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Convince & Convert, LLC  
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the  
Service  
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public  
* To protect against legal liability

Security Of Data  
—————-

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of  
transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100%  
secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your  
Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

“Do Not Track” Signals  
———————-

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can  
set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings  
page of your web browser.

Your Rights  
———–

Convince & Convert, LLC aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct,  
amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your  
account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data,  
please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you  
want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us at info@convinceandconvert.com.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

* To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you  
* To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate  
* To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to  
Convince & Convert, LLC. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal  
Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to  
such requests.

Service Providers  
—————–

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service  
(“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform  
Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these  
tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other  
purpose.

Analytics  
~~~~~~~~~

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our  
Service.

* Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks  
and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and  
monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google  
services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and  
personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to  
Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-  
on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js,  
analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics  
about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the  
Google Privacy &amp; Terms web page:  
<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

Behavioral Remarketing  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Convince & Convert, LLC uses remarketing services to advertise on third party  
websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors  
use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our  
Service.

* Google AdWords

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize  
the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page:  
<http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser  
Add-on – <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> \\- for your web  
browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with  
the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google  
Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the  
Google Privacy &amp; Terms web page:  
<http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

* Twitter

Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.

You can opt-out from Twitter’s interest-based ads by following their  
instructions: <https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405>

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by  
visiting their Privacy Policy page: <https://twitter.com/privacy>

* Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by  
visiting this page: <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions  
from Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral  
Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also  
opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the  
Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA  
<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of  
Canada in Canada <http://youradchoices.ca/> or the European Interactive  
Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>,  
or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit  
Facebook’s Data Policy: <https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>

*LinkedIn  
Remarketing service is provided by LinkedIn, Corporation.  
You can learn more about interest-based advertising from LinkedIn by visiting this page: https://business.linkedin.com/marketing-solutions/ads To opt-out from LinkedIn’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from LinkedIn: https://business.linkedin.com/marketing-solutions/ads  
LinkedIn adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from LinkedIn and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.  
For more information on the privacy practices of LinkedIn, please visit LinkedIn’s Data Policy: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy

Payments  
~~~~~~~~

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case,  
we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is  
provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your  
personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment  
processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI  
Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa,  
Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure  
the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

* Stripe

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

Links To Other Sites  
——————–

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If  
you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s  
site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you  
visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy  
policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy  
——————

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone  
under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that  
your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we  
become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without  
verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information  
from our servers.

Changes To This Privacy Policy  
——————————

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any  
changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior  
to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of  
this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.  
Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this  
page.

Contact Us  
———-

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

* By email: info@convinceandconvert.com

Last updated on  May 11, 2018
